http://www.nationalcase.com/privacy-policy/

RIGID READY ALUMINUM
(single lid & 19” rack mount) *Signature brand - OUR BEST SELLER*
ALPINE ROAD TUFF LAMINATE
(Commercial grade durability)
METAL MASTER ALUMINIUM
(Streamlined performance)
distributor products
PELICAN BRAND CASES (Wide range of applications and proven strength)
PELICAN/STORM
(Proven performance with over 30 stock sizes)
EXPLORER
(Italian made with over 50 stock sizes)
ROTO MOLDED SINGLE LID
(MIL Spec durability in both single lid & 19” Rack mounts)
ROTO MOLDED RACK MOUNT (Durability & Performance)
gallery
blog
contact us
Privacy Policy
We are committed to respecting the privacy of individuals and recognizes the need of people with whom we do business and employees for the appropriate management and protection of any Personal Information that you agree to provide to us.
Our Privacy Management Plan includes guidelines on the collection, storage, use and retention of your Personal Information as follows:
Collection: Our company collects personal information about individuals (clients, suppliers, employees, etc) in order to better manage it's business. Our company will make all reasonable efforts to fully inform such individuals about the planned use/disclosure. We
will limit the collection and use of personal information to that required for valid business purposes or to comply with legislation.
Accuracy: Our company will make every reasonable effort to ensure that the personal information it collects and uses is accurate and complete. Individuals providing personal information will have the opportunity to review and correct their personal information, and on written request by an individual to whom the information relates, the organization will modify the information as required.
Storage: Our company will store personal information using hard copy and/or electronic means in such a way as to prevent unauthorized collection, access, use, disclosure or disposal of the personal information.
Retention: Our company will establish a retention period for all personal information collected. This period may be related to legislation other than PIPEDA (Employment Standards for example).
Disclosure: Our company will not disclose personal information unnecessarily to employees or any third party, unless the effected individual consents.
Access: Our company promotes individual's right of access to personal information about themselves. The employer will provide access to information upon request. Access will be provided according to established procedures. Note: access to a record may be subject to the payment of any fee required according to organization policy.
We will never share, sell or rent information that you supplied to use. Please do not hesitate to ask us if you have any questions regarding our privacy policy.
PROUDLY SERVING & PROUDLY PACKAGING
Defence & Commercial industries
about us
Services & Applications
Protective Foam Inserts
Colour treatments; Anodizing / Power Coat / Alodine
Custom Metal Fabrication
custom products
(single lid & 19” rack mount) *Signature brand - OUR BEST SELLER*
ALPINE ROAD TUFF LAMINATE
(Commercial grade durability)
METAL MASTER ALUMINIUM
(Streamlined performance)
distributor products
PELICAN BRAND CASES (Wide range of applications and proven strength)
PELICAN/STORM
(Proven performance with over 30 stock sizes)
EXPLORER
(Italian made with over 50 stock sizes)
ROTO MOLDED SINGLE LID
(MIL Spec durability in both single lid & 19” Rack mounts)
ROTO MOLDED RACK MOUNT (Durability & Performance)
PRODUCT REQUESTED:
RIGID READY ALUMINUM
(single lid & 19” rack mount) *Signature brand - OUR BEST SELLER*
ALPINE ROAD TUFF LAMINATE
(Commercial grade durability)
METAL MASTER ALUMINIUM
(Streamlined performance)
PELICAN BRAND CASES (Wide range of applications and proven strength)
PELICAN/STORM
(Proven performance with over 30 stock sizes)
EXPLORER
(Italian made with over 50 stock sizes)
ROTO MOLDED SINGLE LID
(MIL Spec durability in both single lid & 19” Rack mounts)
ROTO MOLDED RACK MOUNT (Durability & Performance)
New Products
Yes, I want to get valuable tips and suggestions that can help save money for my business!
REQUEST A QUOTE
×
